Those who ceaselessly hone the art
of killing are known as masters.
These lethal abilities, dutifully
passed down through many generations,
have become what are
called modified bloodlines.
This is the story of one such master,
Hikaru Gero of the Poison Clan
and his greatest challenge yet,
to get married.
No mama, lots of time.
Kill or kiss Let's go!
Let's go!
Here's a photo of Toshiki Hanamaki.
He's the bug master and a long-time
colleague, and also my buddy. Oh, wow!
So this is a guy who's getting married?
He sure got that killer vibe!
I hope you have a great time!
Hey, Kinosaki.
Looks like there's also
a butterfly for you.
Dear Mei Kinosaki,
I hope you are faring well despite this
early summer heat we're experiencing.
Mr.
Gato has informed me of your arrangement.
I cannot tell you how thankful I am you're
assisting with his search for a partner.
Your dedication and
selflessness are so admirable.
I would be honored if you
would attend my humble wedding,
so I may be able to express
my gratitude in person.
Yours truly, Toshiki Hanamaki, Bugmaster.
What a stand-up guy!
I've never been invited
to a wedding before.
Please help.
I want to make sure I'm dressed the part.
After all, it is his special day. You bet!
And a wedding is a great place to meet
new people, including potential paramours.
Mama's gonna need a brand new outfit, too.
Your treat, okie-dokie.
Uh!
I was expecting a bug thing,
but he outdid himself.
It looks like it was ripped straight
from the pages of a fairy tale.
Get out!
Is he dead?
Get out, that's not me!
You haven't been doing
too hot, huh, boss man?
Leaning too hard on
your modified bloodline.
That was only a temporary pick-me-up.
Allow me to introduce you both.
Kinosaki, this is Tsunagi,
the Needle Master.
He's a friend of mine,
like the Bug Master.
Happy to help.
Guess what, boys?
Ad made bank.
Who's up for Undeadsneyland this weekend?
Will we get to meet the real
Undeadsney, Pa? Of course.
I'm planning the most optimal ride route.
I leave it to you.
What a great dad, I think.
With three little clones.
If you're Kinosaki, that must mean you're
the big guy's marriage advisor, huh?
That's gotta be rough. I feel
for you. See? You get it.
We would like to welcome all of our honored
guests who have gathered here today.
The bride and groom
cannot thank you enough.
Now please join us as
we celebrate the union
between Toshiki Hanamaki
and Anna Kawakita.
We have to bring the underworld out
of the darkness and into the light.
The black market organ dealers,
all of the drug cartels.
We must join hands in unity.
Ending this ridiculous forced isolation
once and for all has always been my dream.
Glad you made it.
I only showed up tonight because
you can't seem to take a hint.
Listen,
if you think getting on
my good side is going to
win your family any favors
with my grandmother,
then you're...
Sorry if I gave you the wrong impression.
I just wanted to have a drink together.
If you're up for it, Hikaru Gero.
Would you care to join me?
Afraid it's non-alcoholic,
since you're underage.
Gero, did you hear that story?
Which one?
How the two of them first met.
Anna got into trouble while
mountain climbing and he saved her.
Sounds just like him.
Kinosaki, do you think I'll ever
get to have a wedding this perfect?
No question.
After all, you have me in your corner.
Congrats, Toshiki.
Sure looks like you've got plenty of
happiness and love, don't you, Bug Master?
It ain't fair.
Our couple met in the mountains,
and now spend their days camping.
They're both fans of hiking naturally,
but equally enjoy chatting
around the campfire.
We'll take another Chateaubriand!
And at night, while looking
up at the starry sky...
Get away!
Are you supposed to be
giving a big speech soon?
You'll have to cover for me! Oh, man?
Who's the spider?
You said it, Juliet Jr.
You care about him just as much as I do,
and neither one of us want
anything to ruin his wedding.
I mean, this is the most
important day of Toshiki's life.
Right.
In exactly five minutes,
all of you rush your assigned
entrances and kill whoever you want.
And remember, the more
stiffs, the bigger your bonus.
As soon as Buggy and his master
friends start fighting back, go.
I'll take care of the rest.
While they're distracted, I'll
plant a fancy firework on the bride.
I bet she'll make a pretty
color when she goes off.
There's a picture that the
groom won't be able to forget.
That's my gift too
Well, I guess that's what I get for
hiring mercs on the dark nav fine!
Looks like it's time for plan B?
Firestorm Labyrinth!
Oh, look what you made me do.
What a waste.
And here I was planning on
using those bombs on the guests.
Woo!
Can't be helped.
Guess that's the way
the cookie goes kaboom.
And besides, all I really care
about is paying back that Bugmaster.
The man responsible for stealing
the only true spark in my life.
That's right.
Back in those days, I didn't
give a crap about anything.
School, work, marriage.
I never felt there was
a point to any of it.
Even when I ended up buried in
debt, it didn't seem to matter.
Or when my payment was demanded,
and it meant someone called the Puppet
Master turned me into a hitman for some gang.
All I could think was, whatever.
Well, Yamada, you're a new man.
Miniature bombs have been surgically
planted in your wrist, ankles, and head.
In other words, you're permanently armed.
Press the switch in your back
tooth at the moment of impact.
The explosion will take out
your target and an extremity.
A real explosion roulette.
As of this moment, your only purpose
in life is to go out with a bang.
If things went sideways, I could
take myself out with the target.
For the first time in my life,
I felt the fire live within me, all
thanks to the explosion roulette.
Then he stole it from me.
Gotcha!
At this range, setting off the bomb
in my brain will take him out, too!
Talk about using my head!
I disarmed it for you.
You don't need to be afraid of dying now.
Just like that, it was over!
That inseparable freak took away my only
passion just to feel good about himself!
If he sold what I love,
haven't I also got the right to take
away what he values most in life?
I got new limbs courtesy of the
puppet master as an advance,
made out like a bandit
doing loads of crap jobs,
all the while waiting for this day
to come, and you're not stopping me!
Wait, that's right, you're already dead.
And thank you for being so understanding.
I really appreciate this sushi.
That's a deal!
Sorry.
You say something doesn't matter.
I don't know who you are.
But no decent person holds a
grudge against the bug master.
And we didn't hire a clown
for the entertainment.
Now let's hear from a friend of the groom.
Gedo officially owes me the most expensive
dinner in the history of dinners.
It's really coming down, huh?
Yeah, so much for a
gorgeous view of the sunset.
Please welcome a dear
friend of the groom, Mr.
Hikaru Gedo.
Or not.
Apologies, Gedo came down
with a case of stage fright.
But he prepared a speech he
asked me to read on his behalf.
My name's Mei Kinosaki.
Hey, buddy!
Aren't you a mess, Kevin?
So break out your modified
bloodline! Come on!
What's the deal?
You scared? Let's go!
As if I'd waste it on the likes of you.
Toshiki, Anna, congratulations
on such a wonderful wedding.
If I'm being honest, that's not something
I imagined I would ever hear myself say.
My old friend.
As you know, I'm also hoping
to walk down the aisle soon.
And let me tell you, it's hard as hell.
If only my younger self
could see me now, he'd say.
Don't do it, you're wasting your time.
But here I am.
There's a reason I'm ready to embrace life
and open myself up to someone special.
Because I was lucky enough to meet you.
Toshiki, when I was just some punk
kid going through the motions,
why did you decide to care about me?
On behalf of that kid,
I'd like to thank you.
If you weren't there.
I'm sure I'd be lost.
It didn't matter what you were facing.
You never let it stop you from reaching
out to someone who needed help.
That's what makes you my best friend.
And the coolest guy I've ever known.
I don't want the memory of today
stained with your blood, so beat it.
Seems you're in a bit of trouble, Yamada.
I stand by my products.
I'll release your limiters.
Blow them all away with a
Typhoon-level blast wave.
I've got a real big surprise
for you, Bud Master!
Damn it!
It ain't fair!
You're deeper into the underworld
than a lonely hitman like me.
A weapon of mass destruction more
dangerous than the exploding man.
So how did you have it in
you to embrace me so gently?
Yamada, you're going the wrong way.
Don't tell me you're...
Consider this my farewell gift!
Lastly, Anna, it goes without saying,
but the moment that you found Toshiki,
your happily ever after was guaranteed.
The end.
Thank you for listening.
If you'd be so kind, please
take a look out of the window.
Toshiki, congratulations.
I want to thank you, Kinosaki.
Not just for the speech, but
for helping Gero find a wife.
It's no biggie.
My contributions are small potatoes
compared to all you've given him.
I mean, even when Gero was a moody
teenager, you never left his side.
While that may be true, I'm the
one who should be thanking him.
Huh?
With the power dynamic
between our families,
someone in his position shouldn't be
my friend, much less attend my wedding.
I'm fortunate.
What power dynamic?
I was kind of under the impression both
of you were masters and there wasn't one.
The Hanamaki Bugmasters
started with venomous insects,
the Tsunagi Needlemasters with poison.
There are other masters that specialize
in diseases and physical ailments.
But our branch families,
we recognize the Poison Clan as our ancestors
and answer to them without question.
There are only five great
families at the top.
The Gero family, the Arima,
the Dogo, the Kirishima, and the Nasuka.
The entire society of masters
is made up of their families,
branch families, and their offshoots.
Clans not related to them are rare.
If one of the great families told
a branching one their time was up,
they would off themselves
without complaint.
That's how low we are.
Listen carefully, Toshiki.
Our family we live only thanks
to the ghetto's good graces.
For centuries,
the heads of the five great households
have been toying with human lives.
They're absolute monsters.
Never assume they share any of our values.
They see the lives of enemies and allies
as nothing but pawns to enrich their clans.
So unless you want our line to
end, shut up and do as you're told.
Oh, there's no need for that.
Please, raise your heads.
This is Master Hikaru.
He was tentatively named
heir the other day.
I wasn't afraid when I first met Gero.
What struck me most was
how he seemed, well...
We are but lowly worms.
We owe our very lives to the
generosity of the Gero family.
That's all we have time for.
Yes, sir. Thank you, sir.
Master Hikaru, please use and discard this
boy's life as if it were a lowly insect.
I'm back up here!
He doesn't look like an insect.
He was just a guy even though everyone
else around him was terrified.
I saw a normal kid yep a regular old joe
when I told pops we were drinking buddies.
His mouth started foaming
and he passed out.
Ms. Kinosaki.
It'll be a hundred times more difficult
than it was for me or the Needle Clan.
But please, help him find
us happily ever after.
I will, but yeah, it's gonna be tough.
He freezes up at just
the sight of a woman.
Yeah sounds about right.
I know where you're coming from though.
He's a really good guy.
Rest assured, I'm going to find them.
His perfect match to share his life with.
Since when did Kino
Saki become such
good friends with my work buddies?
What What are those three plotting?
Let me tag along on your next fight.
Don't you have a brood to take care of?
Before you go, a hundred
million blessings, my friend.
Happy honeymoon!
Uh yeah he had like a
pointy thing on the end of
a pole and was pretty
good at waving it around.
Uh-huh but apart from that he
was sort of normal great work
as always right i'm sending over
the next list of masters now.
Good luck wiping out those Hitman.
I'll be creepy, oh, make a voice
It's so good.
No, no love has been filled.
You love me from my Step, baby.
I want to be moving altogether.
I want to watch pretty much.
You love me from my Step, baby.
I want to watch this real dance.
I'll let you protect me.
10,000 yen a day!
Come on!
Meet him to the punch!
You gotta be over the moon.
Please dine.
Next time, the Hitman Hunter.